{
    "id": "4883027218d5449b898cdaa3049e22d4",
    "title": "Words followed by particular prepositions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0e49844d5cc8412eb464f96e9d5fcc7a",
            "title": "Words Followed By Particular Prepositions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "One must never deviate ……………….. the right path.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "to",
                        "with",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Eventually she acceded ……………….. my requests.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is no cure ...................... many forms of cancer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "against"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is keen ………………….. pursuing higher education in the US.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "on",
                        "at",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His latest novels make several allusions …………………. Hindu Mythology.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was anxious .....................… contact his parents.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "about",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has an aptitude ………………… music.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "for",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The indulgent mother is always blind …………………. her child’s faults.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "to",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was brought ……………….. by his grandparents.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "up",
                        "over",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is addicted …………………. drinking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "from",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}